http://www.cgspllc.com/privacy-policy

Design Firms and Consultants
By Practice Area:
Representative Matters
By Client Type:
Design Firms and Consultants
By Practice Area:
Disclaimer
All materials and links on this web site are designed for informational purposes alone. The transmission and display of the information contained here is not intended to create, and receipt or viewing of it does not constitute, an attorney-client relationship. This site does not constitute advice on legal matters.
If you are interested in retaining the services of Conner Gwyn Schenck PLLC, we would be delighted to send you additional information about our qualifications, experience, and standard terms of engagement. Please do not send us any confidential information without first speaking with an attorney listed under the contact us page. The materials on this web site are intended, but not guaranteed, to reflect current legal developments and the current state of the law. We do not, however, represent, warrant, or guarantee they will be complete, accurate, or up to date when you view them. Conner Gwyn Schenck PLLC is not responsible for any third-party content accessed through this web site. Any reference to third-party information, products, or services linked to this web site does not constitute an expressed or implied endorsement by Conner Gwyn Schenck PLLC.
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Conner Gwyn Schenck PLLC collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the https://cgspllc.com/ website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Conner Gwyn Schenck PLLC.Personal identification informationWe may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways in connection with activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.Non-personal identification informationWe may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about User’s means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.Web browser cookiesOur Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.How we use collected informationConner Gwyn Schenck PLLC may collect and use User’s personal information for the following purposes:To improve our SiteWe may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.How we protect your informationWe adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and reasonable security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, transaction information and data stored on our Site. Although we place a priority on the security of personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us through the Site.Sharing your personal informationWe do not sell, trade, or rent User’s personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.Third party websitesUsers may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.Changes to this privacy policyConner Gwyn Schenck PLLC has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.Your acceptance of these termsBy using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.Contacting usIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, please contact us at:Conner Gwyn Schenck PLLC 3141 John Humphries Wynd Suite 100 Raleigh, NC 27612(919) 789-9242mboyle@cgspllc.com This document was last updated on December 17, 2014
